RG 079:005, Department of Environmental Protection: Air, Waste and Water
Connecticut State Library
- Series 14. Bureau of Water Management, 1920-1979
  - Permitting, Enforcement, and Remediation Division, 1928-1979; bulk 1969-1977
    - Reports, 1997-051
      - Bridgeport (Box 2)
        - Bridgeport Brass Division, Seymour, 1971 (Box 2)
        - Remington Arms Co., Bridgeport, 1972; 2 reports (Box 2)
        - Remington Electric Shaver Div., Sapery Rand Corp., Bridgeport, 1972 (Box 2)
        - Sikorsky Aircraft, Div. Of United Aircraft Corp., Bridgeport, 1973 (Box 2)
        - Specifications Plating Inc., Bridgeport, 1976; 2 reports (Box 2)
        - Specifications Plating Inc., Bridgeport, 1975 (Box 2)
        - Specification Plating Inc., Bridgeport Discharge Control Plant drawings, 1976; 3 reports (Box 2)
        - Son Oil Company, Bridgeport, 1946 (Box 2)
        - Remington Arms Co., Bridgeport, 1973 (Box 2)
        - Steel Point Station - United Illuminating Co., Bridgeport, 1976 (Box 3)
      - Bristol (Box 3)
        - Associated Spring Inc., Bristol, 1978, 1979 (Box 3)
        - Wallace Barnes Division - Associated Spring Corp., Bristol, 1968 October, 1969 December, 1974 May, 1974 June (Box 3)
        - The Bristol Brass Corporation, Bristol, 1968 (Box 3)
        - Comerford Spring Division, Inc., Bristol, 1967 (Box 3)
        - New Departure Division, General Motors Corp., Bristol, 1959 (Box 3)
        - The Ingraham Company, Bristol, 1964 February, 1964 July (Box 3)
        - Superior Electric Co., Bristol, 1977 (Box 3)
      - Brookfield (Box 3)
        - Proposed Shopping Center, Town of Brookfield, CT, 1972 March, 1973 January, 1973 December (Box 3)
        - A.J. Tuck Company, Brookfield, 1979 (Box 3)
      - Cheshire (Box 3)
        - Consolidated Industries, Cheshire, (drawings/plans), 1974 (Box 3)
        - Consolidated Industries, Division of Kearny-National, Inc., 1971 (Box 3)
        - MicroTech Division, Waveline Inc., Cheshire, 1972 (Box 3)
        - Dot Fastener Company, Cheshire, 1972, 1974 (Box 3)
        - The Holgrath Corporation, Cheshire, 1974 (Box 3)
        - Microtech Corp., Cheshire, 1971 (Box 3)
        - Siemens Corp., Medical Systems Division, Cheshire, 1975; 2 folders (Box 3)
      - Chester (Box 3)
        - Town of Chester, CT, Castle View Estates, 1975 (Box 3)
        - C.J. Bates & Son, Inc., Chester, 1968, 1969, 1972 September (Box 3)
      - Clinton (Box 3)
        - Chesebrough-Ponds, Inc., Clinton, 1976, 1977, July. 1975, August. 2975, 1974, 1969 (2 copies), 1968 (2 copies), 1958, January & February. 1961, 1960, June. 30. 1969, 1969 (Box 3)
        - Bostitch Division of Textron, Inc., Universal Wire Plant, Clinton, 1969, February. 1970, April. 1970 (Box 3)
      - Coventry (Box 4)
        - Lake Rehabilitation Report, ALand Use@ Coventry, 1975 March (Box 4)
        - Lake Rehabilitation Report, ARoads@ Coventry, 1975 April (Box 4)
        - Lake Rehabilitation Report, AHealth@ Coventry, 1975 June (Box 4)
        - Greater Hartford Community Development Corp., Hartford, 1974 Hartford (Box 4)
      - Cromwell (Box 4)
        - Alcap Manufacturing Co., Inc., Cromwell, 1974 September 6, 1974 September 12 (Box 4)
      - Danbury (Box 4)
        - Solids Handling- Margerie Lake Water Treatment Plant, Danbury, 1979 (Box 4)
        - Amphenol, R.F. Division of Bunker-Ramo Corp., Danbury, 1973 (Box 4)
        - Boehringer Ingelheim Limited, USA, Danbury, 1976 (Box 4)
        - Boehringer Ingelheim Limited, USA, Pump Station & Wet Well, Danbury, 1977 (Box 4)
        - Empire Fur Associates, Inc., Danbury, 1952 (Box 4)
        - Danbury Fur Cutting and Hat Shop Inspection, Danbury, 1937 (Box 4)
        - New Medallic Art Co. Plant, Danbury, 1972 (Box 4)
        - Gar Precision Products, Inc. Division of Helicoil Corp., Danbury, 1963 (Box 4)
        - Heli-Coil Products, Danbury, 1977 (Box 4)
        - Medallic Art Company, Danbury, 1976 (Box 4)
        - Qualitron Corporation, Danbury, 1973 (Box 4)
        - Microtronics of Danbury, 1979 (Box 4)
        - Risdon Manufacturing Company, Danbury, 1973 March 3, 1973 April (Box 4)
      - Derby (Box 4)
        - Sanitary Sewers, Lift Station and Appurtenances, Derby, 1966 (Box 4)
        - The W.E. Bassett Company, Derby, 1966, 1969, 1972 (Box 4)
      - Durham (Box 4)
        - Durham Manufacturing Co., Durham, 1972 (Box 4)
        - W.A. Parsons Co., Inc., Durham, 1976 (Box 4)
      - East Hartford (Box 4)
        - United Aircraft Corp., East Hartford, (report by Mr. Martin, Director State Water Commission to Members of Commission), 1947 (Box 4)
        - Case Brothers, Inc., East Hartford, 1968 (Box 4)
        - Sanitary Paper Mills, Inc., East Hartford, 1955 (Box 4)
        - Doll Paper Company, East Hartford, 1965, 1966; 2 copies (Box 4)
        - New England Chrome Plating Co., East Hartford, 1978; 3 reports (Box 4)
        - Sanitary Paper Mills, Inc., East Hartford, 1960-1963 (Box 4)
        - Pratt & Whitney Aircraft, East Hartford, appendix to other report, 1947, 1967, 1969, 1947 (Box 4)
        - United Aircraft Research Laboratories, East Hartford, 1970 September, 1971 January; 2 copies each (Box 4)
        - East Hartford Water Pollution Control Plant, East Hartford, 1968 (Box 4)
        - Pratt & Whitney Aircraft, East Hartford, 1968, 1973; 6 reports (Box 5)
      - East Lyme (Box 5)
        - Rocky Neck State Park, East Lyme, 1966, 1968, 1966 April; 3 copies (Box 5)
        - State Farm for Women, Niantic, 1927, 1966, 1967; 2 copies for 1927 (Box 5)
        - National Guard Camp at Niantic, East Lyme, 1934, 1935 (Box 5)
        - The Seaside Sanitarium at Crescent Beach, East Lyme, 1928 (Box 5)
        - Howard Johnson’s Motor Lodge, East Lyme, 1972 (Box 5)
        - Howard Johnson’s Motor Lodge, East Lyme, (plans), 1972 (Box 5)
      - Enfield (Box 5)
        - Intercepting Sewer and Pumping Station for Town of Enfield, 1935 (Box 5)
      - Essex (Box 5)
        - The Verplex Company, Essex, 1959; 2 copies (Box 5)
      - Fairfield (Box 5)
        - Handy & Harman, Fairfield, 1967, 1968 (Box 5)
        - ESB Incorporated, Fairfield, 1968 (Box 5)
      - Glastonbury (Box 5)
        - Glastonbury Sanitary Landfill, Hearing Transcript, 1976 January 30; 2 copies (Box 5)
        - Town of Glastonbury, Hearing Transcript, Oct. 28, 1976 (2 copies), 1976, Feb. 3, 1977 (2 copies) (Box 5)
        - Arbor Acres, Marlborough, 1979 (Box 5)
        - Herman Roser & Sons, Inc., Glastonbury, 1949 (Box 5)
        - J.T. Slocomb Company, Glastonbury, 1978 February, 1978 July; 2 reports (Box 5)
        - Matson Mills Inc., South Glastonbury, 1945 (Box 5)
      - Greenwich (Box 5)
        - Town of Greenwich (Sludge Composting Program), 1979 (Box 5)
        - Electrolux Corp., Old Greenwich, 1940, 1971 (Box 5)
        - American Felt Company, Glenville, 1945 (Box 5)
        - The Disposal of Refuse in Greenwich, 1935 (Box 5)
        - American Can Company, Greenwich, 1966 (Box 5)
        - Acceptability of Industrial Effluents to Water and Wastewater Management Resources, Town of Greenwich, 1972 (Box 5)
        - Fairview Country Club, Greenwich, 1966 (Box 5)
        - Round Hill Country Club, Greenwich, 1956 (Box 5)
        - American Felt Company, Glenville, 1956, 1968 (Box 5)
      - Griswold (Box 5)
        - Town of Griswold, Subdivision (?) Map, (Glasgo), 1968 (Box 5)
      - Groton, 1928-1979 (Box 6)
        - Arwood Corp., Groton, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
        - The Christie Plating Co., Groton, 1974, 1975, 1976; 3 reports (Box 6)
        - General Dynamics Corp., Electric Boat Div., Groton, 1976, 1977, 1978, 1979; 2 reports for 1977 (Box 6)
        - Mystic Oral School for the Deaf, Mystic, 1928 (Box 6)
        - Chas. Pfizer & Co. Inc., Groton, 1967, 1969, 1970, 1971; 2 reports for 1969 + 1970 (Box 6)
        - Pfizer Inc., Groton, 1977, 1978, 1979; 2 reports (Box 6)
        - Pfizer Inc., Groton, 1976 April 28, 1978 March 31, 1978 June 21, 1978 December 31 (Box 6)
        - Pharmaceutical Manufacturing - Point Source Category (EPA publication), December 1976, June 1980 (Box 6)
        - Pfizer, Inc., Groton, 1975 (Box 7)
      - Guilford (Box 7)
        - Waverly Chemical, Co. Inc., Guilford, 1969 (Box 7)
        - Maple Shade Farm, Inc., Guilford, 1967 (Box 7)
        - Kenyon Marine, Guilford, 1979 (Box 7)
        - Charles Bruning Comp., Division of Addressograph Multigraph Corp., Guilford, 1973 (Box 7)
      - Haddam (Box 7)
        - Connecticut River Ecological Survey, 1974 January (Box 7)
        - CT River Ecological Study, 13th semi-annual report, 1971 (Box 7)
        - CT River Ecological Survey, 1973 May-April, 1974, 1975 February (Box 7)
        - The Sibley Company, Haddam, 1968, 1974 (Box 7)
        - Journal of the Fisheries Research Board of Canada, 1973 (Box 7)
        - CT River Study, 10th semi-annual report, 1970 April (Box 7)
        - CT River Ecological Study, 12th semi-annual report, 1971 April 21 (Box 7)
        - CT River Ecological Study, 14th semi-annual report, 1972 April 21; 3 copies (Box 7)
        - CT River Ecological Study, 15th semi-annual report, 1972 October 21; 3 copies (Box 7)
        - CT River Ecological Study-Yankee Atomic Power Plant, Haddam Neck, 1972 (Box 7)
        - CT River Ecological Study- Water Temps, 1966-1969, 1970 April (Box 7)
        - Final Report on Possible Alternatives to Chlorination for Controlling Fouling in Power Station Cooling Water Systems, 1976 April (Box 7)
        - CT River Study, 11th semi-annual report, 1970 October 21 (Box 7)
        - CT River Study, 9th semi-annual report, 1969 October 21 (Box 7)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Company, Haddam Neck Plant, Circa 1972, 1977 March 31; 2 copies (Box 7)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Company, Permits & Approvals, circa 1960 (Box 7)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Company, Haddam Neck, Addenda No. 1 to Env. Report Operating License Stage Appendix B, circa 1972 (Box 7)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Company, Haddam Neck, Addenda No 2, Env. Report Operating License Stage Appendix C, circa 1971 (Box 7)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Company, Haddam Neck, Addenda No 3, Env. Report Operating License Stage Appendix C, circa 1972 (Box 7)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Company, Haddam Neck, Addenda No 4, Env. Report Operating License Stage Appendix B, circa 1973 (Box 7)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Company, Haddam Neck, Addenda No 5, Env. Report Operating License Stage Appendix C, circa 1972-1973 (Box 7)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Company, Haddam Neck, Addenda No 6, Env. Report Operating License Stage, Appendix B, 1973 (Box 7)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Company, Haddam Neck, Addenda No 7, Env. Report Operating License Stage Appendix C, 1973 (Box 7)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Company, Haddam Neck, Addenda No 8, Env. Report Operating License Stage Appendix C, 1973 (Box 7)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Company, Haddam Neck, Addenda No 9, Env. Report Operating License Stage Appendix C, 1974 (Box 7)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Comp., Haddam Neck, circa 1960-1972, Jul. 1965-Oct. 1971, circa 1970 (Box 8)
        - CT River Study, 10th semi-annual report, 1970 April 21 (Box 8)
        - CT River Ecological Study, 12th semi-annual report, 1971 April 21 (Box 8)
        - CT River Ecological Study, 16th semi-annual report, 1973 April 21 (Box 8)
        - New England River Basins Modeling Project -Final report, 1974 February (Box 8)
        - The Sibley Company, Haddam, 1977 (Box 8)
      - Hamden (Box 8)
        - Giering Metal Finishing, Inc. Hamden, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1971 (Box 8)
      - Hartford (Box 8)
        - Arrow-Hart, Inc., Hartford, 1973, 1974 July, 1974 December, 1975 March (Box 8)
        - The CapeWell Manufacturing Co., Hartford, 1973 (Box 8)
        - Capital City Engraving Co., Inc., Hartford, 1974 (Box 9)
        - Colt Industries, Firearms Division, Hartford, Oct. 1973, 1975, Dec. 1975, Jul. 1975, May 1976(2 copies), Sep. 1976, Feb. 1977 (Box 9)
        - Greater Hartford Community Development Corp., Hartford, 1974; 2 copies (Box 9)
        - Whitney Chain Div., Jeffrey Mfg. Co., Hartford, 1974 February, 1974 July (Box 9)
        - Neilsen Tool and Die Company, Hartford, 1979 August; 2 copies (Box 9)
        - The Stanley P. Rockwell Co., Hartford, 1974 (Box 9)
        - Suisman and Blumenthal, Inc., Hartford, Jun. 1969, Feb. 1970, Jun. 1970, Feb. 1971, Oct. 1974, Dec. 1974, Sep. 1978, Dec. 1978, Feb. 1979 (Box 9)
        - Veeder-Root, Hartford, 1973 May, 1974 July (Box 9)
      - Killingly (Box 9)
        - Proposed Additions to Waste Water Treatment Plant, Killingly, 1979 October (Box 9)
        - Frito-Lay, Killingly, 1978, 1979 July, 1979 August, 1979 September (Box 9)
        - Rogers Corp., Rogers, 1969 March (Box 9)
      - Lebanon (Box 9)
        - Lebanon Industrial Park, Lebanon, 1975 December; 2 copies (Box 9)
      - Ledyard (Box 9)
        - “The Highlands,” Ledyard, 1974 May (Box 9)
        - Apartment Complex, Howell Property, Ledyard, 1970 February; 2 copies (Box 9)
        - Lifetime Homes, Ledyard, 1964, 1967, 1969, 1970, 1971 (Box 9)
        - Pfizer & Co. Inc., Ledyard, 1966 (Box 9)
      - Lisbon (Box 10)
        - Lisbon Textile Company, Lisbon, 1969 October, 1976 (Box 10)
        - The Lisbon Textile Prints, Inc., Lisbon, 1976 April, 1977 June; 2 copies (Box 10)
      - Litchfield (Box 10)
        - A Preliminary Study of the Groundwater of the Litchfield Hills Region, Litchfield, 1970 September (Box 10)
        - Hotchkiss School, Litchfield, 1964 June (Box 10)
        - Bantam Lake, 1964 June, 1964 August (Box 10)
        - Aerospace Division, Universal Oil Products Comp., Bantam, December 1968, May 1971, October 1971 (Box 10)
      - Manchester (Box 10)
        - Multi-Circuits, Inc., Manchester, 1974 October (Box 10)
        - Manchester Industrial Park Stormwater, Manchester, 1977-1978 (Box 10)
      - Mansfield (Box 10)
        - CT Agricultural College, 1927 (Box 10)
        - Mansfield State Training School and Hospital, Mansfield Depot, October 1969, March 1966, February 1965, August 1964 (Box 10)
        - Preliminary Design Report on Sewer connections to Willimantic, 1970 April (Box 10)
        - University of CT, Storrs, 1961 January, 1963 January, 1969 July; 3 copies (Box 10)
      - Meriden (Box 10)
        - Union Manufacturing Comp., Meriden, 1974 June, 1978 June (Box 10)
        - J.B. Coggins Manufacturing Co., Meriden, March 1960, June 1968, January 1969, February 1971 (Box 10)
        - Informal Hearing, J.B. Coggins Manufacturing Co., Industrial Waste Problem, Meriden, 1959 August (Box 10)
        - The Miller Company, Meriden, 1968 September (Box 10)
        - American Circuitron, Inc., South Meriden, 1976 October (Box 10)
        - Rockwell Silver, Meriden, 1977 September (Box 10)
        - The Napier Company, Meriden, 1968 November (Box 10)
        - Pollution of Harbor Brook & Remedial Measures, Meriden, 1945 November (Box 10)
        - Cedar Wood Valley Subdivision, Meriden, 1965 October (Box 10)
        - Meriden Planning Commission Report on Summitwood, 1977 September (Box 10)
      - Middlefield (Box 11)
        - The Leisure Group, Inc., Lyman Products Division, Middlefield, 1974 July (Box 11)
        - Middlefield Sampling Program Beseck Lake and Coginchaug River, Middlefield, 1976 January (Box 11)
      - Montville (Box 11)
        - Continental Can Company, Uncasville, 1968 April (Box 11)
        - CT Light & Power Company, Montville Station, 1976 June, 1968 December; 2 copies (Box 11)
        - Thames River Paper Mill, Uncasville, 1972 (Box 11)
      - Middletown (Box 11)
        - Middletown Water Treatment Plant, Middletown, 1965 October; 2 copies (Box 11)
        - Russell Manufacturing Company, Middletown, 1950 March (Box 11)
        - Pratt & Whitney Aircraft, Middletown, 1968 January, 1970 (Box 11)
        - Pratt & Whitney Aircraft, Environmental Radioactivity at Canel, Middletown, 1961 (Box 11)
        - Sawmill Brook Race Track, Middletown, hearing transcript, Report & Recommendation of the Hearing Examiner, 1974, 1976 April, 1976, 1976 August, 1976 September (Box 11)
        - Safeway Products, Inc., Middletown, 1977 (Box 11)
        - The North & Judd Division, Gulf & Western Manufacturing, Middletown, 1977, 1978, 1979 (Box 11)
        - NU Steam electric generating station, Middletown, 1978 (Box 11)
      - Moodus (Box 11)
        - Brownell & Company Inc., Moodus, 1976 July, 1977 August, 1977 December (Box 11)
      - Morris (Box 11)
        - Special Products Division, Torrington Company, East Morris, 1979 (Box 11)
        - Morris Plant of Torrington Special Products, Div. Of Torrington Comp., Morris, 1978 August (Box 11)
      - Millstone - Reports (Box 12)
        - The Millstone Point Company, Waterford, (exhibits A-K), exhibit 3-8, 1974, 1969-1970, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
        - A Monitoring Program on the Ecology of the Marine Environment of the Millstone Point, Waterford, 1973 (Box 12)
        - Application for a Certificate of environmental compatibility & public need, Millstone Power Station Unit #3, Waterford, 1973 (Box 12)
        - Final environmental statement - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Waterford, 1973 (Box 12)
        - The Millstone Point Company, Waterford, 1973 (Box 12)
        - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, units 1,2,3, Waterford, 1976 (Box 12)
        - Dye Diffusion Survey, Millstone Point, 1971 (Box 12)
      - Middletown (Box 13)
        - United Illuminating, Coke works generating plant effect of heated cooling water discharge on the temperature distribution of New Haven Harbor, 1971 (Box 13)
        - Safeway Products, Inc., Middletown, 1977 (Box 13)
        - Hartford Electric Light Company, Middletown Station, 1976 (Box 13)
        - NU-Helco, Middletown Steam Electric Generating Station, 1976 (Box 13)
      - Milford (Box 13)
        - Secondi Bros. Service Station, Milford, 1971 (Box 13)
        - Milford Rivet and Machine Company, Milford, 1967 (Box 13)
        - Robertshaw Controls Company, Milford Division, 1968; 2 copies (Box 13)
        - Power Semiconductors, Inc., Devon, 1974 August, 1974 February; 1974 2 copies (Box 13)
        - CT Light & Power Comp., Devon Station, 1976 (Box 13)
        - NU, CL&P, Milford, Devon Station, 1978 (Box 13)
        - Riverview Condominiums, Milford, 1975 January, 1975 August; 1975 January 2 reports (Box 13)
        - Rostand Manufacturing Co., Milford, 1974 (Box 13)
        - Silver Sands State Park, Milford, 1978 (Box 13)
      - Millstone - Reports (Box 14)
        - Millstone Nuclear Power Station units 1,2,3, Waterford, 1974-1976 (Box 14)
        - Millstone Nuclear Power Station unit 3, 1973 (Box 14)
        - CT Yankee Atomic Power Company, Haddam Neck plant, hearing transcripts - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, unit No 3 (Box 14)
          - vol. I, 1974 June 24 (Box 14)
          - vol. II, 1974 June 25 (Box 14)
          - vol. III, 1974 June 26 (Box 14)
        - Thermal Effluent - Millstone Point, 1974 (Box 14)
        - A Mathematical Model for evaluating the effect of Power plant entrainment on populations near millstone point, 1973 April-1973 September (Box 14)
        - A Monitoring program on the ecology of the marine environment of Millstone Point, 1973 (Box 14)
      - Naugatuck (Box 15)
        - Glennridge Sewer Study, Naugatuck, 1972, 1978 (Box 15)
        - Dooval Tool and Manufacturing Inc., Naugatuck, 1971 April, 1969-1971,1971 May (Box 15)
        - The Naugatuck Glass Co., Naugatuck, 1975 May 30, 1975 February 27, 1975 June 4 (Box 15)
        - Risdon Manufacturing Comp., Naugatuck, 1968 (Box 15)
        - Roberts Plating Company, Inc., Naugatuck, 1969 (Box 15)
        - Uniroyal Footwear Plant, Naugatuck, (plans), 1968, 1975, 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
        - Uniroyal Chemical Division, Naugatuck, 1967 October & December 1968 (Box 15)
      - New Britain (Box 15)
        - The Fafnir Bearing Company, New Britain, 1970 (Box 15)
        - The Fafnir Bearing Company, Div. Of Textron, Inc., New Britain, 1974, 1976, 1978 April 1978, 1978 September (Box 15)
        - Dept. 23, Brass Plating Line, The Stanley Works, New Britain, 1973 January (Box 15)
        - Dept. 9,16,27, The Stanley Works, New Britain, 1974 March (Box 15)
        - General Electric Comp., Housewares Division, New Britain, 1968 (Box 15)
        - J.H. Metal Finishing, Inc., New Britain, 1976 (Box 15)
        - New Britain Hand Tool Division, Litton Industrial Products, Inc., 1976, 1979 (Box 15)
        - Macristy Industries, Inc., CT Stamping and Bending Div., New Britain, 1976, 1977 (Box 15)
        - New Britain Machine Div., Litton Industrial Products, Inc., New Britain, 1977 (Box 15)
        - The Pape Plating Co., New Britain, 1979 March, 1979 May (Box 15)
        - E.R. & Preliminary Plans -- Pape Plating, 1979; 2 copies (Box 16)
        - Final Report and Engineering Specifications -- Papa Plating, Inc. (Box 16)
        - Report. on Proposed Industrial Waste Treatment System--Sherman Tomasso Concrete, Inc. - no date?, 1968 (Box 16)
        - Stanley Tools -- Room layout showing waste treatment facilities, 1972 (Box 16)
        - Proposed Process Waste Treatment Facilities, 1971 October (Box 16)
      - New Hartford (Box 16)
        - Industrial Waste Treatment -- Waring Products, 1969 January (Box 16)
      - New Haven (Box 16)
        - New Haven Water Company -- Submission of Construction Plans & Specs., 1973 February 6 (Box 16)
        - New Haven Water Company -- Contract Drawing & Specs., 1973 January (Box 16)
        - New Haven Water Company -- Lake Whitney Filter Plant Wastewater Effluent, 1972 August (Box 16)
        - Report on Preliminary Design of the East Shore Water Pollution Abatement Plant, 1973 March 3 (Box 16)
        - Preliminary Engineering Report -- C. Cowles & Company, 1976 September 30 (Box 16)
        - Final Eng. Report. for Industrial Waste Treatment -- C. Cowles & Company, 1978 March 1 (Box 16)
        - Final Eng. Report. for Industrial Waste Treatment -- H.B. Ives Company, 1976 February 26 (Box 16)
        - Preliminary Eng. Report. -- H.B. Ives Company, 1975 July 29 (Box 16)
        - Industrial Waste Treatment System -- H.B. Ives Company, 1964 April 14 (Box 16)
        - Environmental Report on Coke Works Site -- United Illuminating Co., 1972 (Box 16)
        - Preliminary Eng. Report. for Industrial Waste Treatment -- Mite Corp., 1978 November 9 (Box 16)
        - Eng. Report. for Industrial Sewage Treatment -- Mite Corp., 1969 April (Box 16)
        - Report to Olin-Winchester Waterwater Sampling and Flow Monitoring Program for the New Haven Facilities Phase II - Quantification and Qualification of Process Discharges, 1978 September 28 (Box 16)
        - Wastewater Management Report -- The Pond Lily Company, 1977 August (Box 16)
        - Wastewater Management Program -- The Pond Lily Company, 1977 April (Box 16)
        - Eng. Report. -- Seamless Rubber Co., 1971 June 21 (Box 16)
        - Supplementary Eng. Report. -- Seamless Rubber Co., 1970 May 19 (Box 16)
        - Eng. Report. -- Seamless Rubber Co., 1968 November 13 (Box 16)
        - Engineering Report for Supplemental Industrial Waste Treatment -- Sargent & Co., 1975 January 17 (Box 16)
        - Hypographic Survey of the Waters Adjacent to the English Generating Station for UI, 1971 July (Box 17)
        - New Haven Harbor Hydrographic Study for UI, 1970 December (Box 17)
        - Environmental Report Coke Works Site for UI, 1971 June (Box 17)
        - Coke Works Generating Plant - Effect of Heated Cooling Water Discharge on the Temperature Distribution of New Haven Harbor for UI, 1971 February; 3 reports (Box 17)
        - Buoyant Jet Discharge Model Study for Coke Works Power Plant - New Haven Harbor, 1972 January (Box 17)
        - Draft Environmental Statement - Coke Works Electric Generating Plant, 1972 June (Box 17)